Broken and lost lies
the last component somewhere
I look for it, and follow the distant stars
to the ends of a rainbow sky
Through the cracks faint light
leaks into my vision to lure me onward
and I walk my path as in a daydream
The growing strength of my bonds
and my ability to redo it all
will not let go of all my heart holds
Help me retrieve it
I will connect the bits and pieces,
and once I look at the ring they make,
I will change it for my sake
and spin it anew,
so that I can be myself again
You...
broke your promise, didn't you?
Thank goodness!
You're awake!
It's all right.
They're gone now.
It's not cut, is it?
Back then...
It seemed like a fragment of a memory.
I don't remember.
Did those girls do that to you before?
But cutting a girl's hair is criminal! Criminal, I say!
But...
Before I lost my memories, and even now,
it seems inevitable that they'll cut my hair.
I...
It's more than petty hatred. I feel like I'm despised.
I could definitely feel their animosity.
They said "promise," right?
Is that...
It seems that before you lost your memories,
you must've made a promise with those girls,
and since you lost your memories, you ended up breaking that promise?
I doubt they'll tell us the whole story, even if we ask them.
They might even take advantage of your memory loss and lie to you.
As such, I must still recommend that you keep your memory loss a secret.
The people you work with don't seem like bad people,
but we don't even know what your oldest friends, Toma and Shin, are like.
And now that someone harbors animosity toward you,
there's no telling how information might leak out.
I know.
I don't know what promise I made to those girls,
but I broke that promise.
Because of that, I hurt someone or made them sad...
Are you all better now?
Yeah. Sorry for making you worry.
I'm not totally up to speed yet, but...
It's okay. We'll help you out.
Sawa, you're so reliable!
No, Mine, you're helping out, too.
I think we can trust them.
Hey...
There's something different about you.
Ah!
You think so?
I thought everything was going well, but I spoke too soon!
If you asked me what it was, I couldn't tell you,
but something feels different.
She's been spacing out a lot lately, but then again, she's always been like that.
Great cover!
That's right...
Today we're meeting about the trip.
Trip?
You're not supposed to go too, are you?
Is everyone supposed to be at the meeting?
What are you talking about?
It's our orientation trip for part-timers,
so we talked about how we should all meet to discuss it.
I meant, do you think everyone can come?
Of course.
At first Shin said he couldn't make it because he was studying for exams, but...
Taking occasional breaks may improve the efficacy of your exam studying.
So Shin said he'd come after all.
So in the end, we can all go. Don't you remember?
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
Hey, you don't look it at all.
That's not true...
Three days and two nights on an island trip.
Is it all right for me to go in my current state?
This first hurdle is set too high, right?
It'll be challenging to not make any mistakes during the trip.
That said, it could also be a chance at getting your memories back,
so we should think optimistically.
Yeah.
You.
Yes?
What have you been mumbling to yourself over there?
Take this to table three.
A birthday cake?
I haven't seen one of those in a while.
Happy birthday to you. Happy birthday to you...
Happy birthday, dear...
I killed...
I...
...killed a man.
What was that? That was Shin, wasn't it?
Was that another memory?
Killed?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's nothing.
I hope it won't rain.
Huh?
Oh, yeah, you're right.
There'd be no point, if it rained and you couldn't see it.
Couldn't see what?
What do you mean, "see what?" It was your idea.
Mine?
This isn't good!
Shin's looking right at you, too!
It was you who said you wanted to see the Mnemid meteor shower.
Just go along with it!
Ah, that's right.
What else could it be?
I forgot.
You're forgetting too much!
According to the weekly weather report, it should be mostly clear.
I'm sure it'll be pretty.
I'm looking forward to the meteor shower.
I said I wanted to see it...
Hey.
Are you all right with your studying?
I'm going because it's all right.
True enough.
By the way, Kento, you're a graduate student in math, right?
Why don't you have him teach you?
I don't mind, but organize your questions beforehand.
That way, I won't waste my time on meaningless problems.
We're all here.
Now, I'd like to begin our meeting concerning the island trip this weekend, August 8th.
To strengthen inter-staff relations at Meido no Hitsuji,
I planned on bringing us together under one roof.
But, well, let's leave out the serious talk.
Everyone, please enjoy yourselves.
Looks like we made it out okay.
But there's so much I don't know.
It might be inevitable that everyone thinks I'm acting weird.
At the moment, Mine and Shin are particularly dangerous.
They look like they suspect something.
Oh yeah, it might be a good idea to ask more questions that could give us hints about your memories.
That's right.
It would be nice if I could.
I'm sorry. I said I'd do my best, but it's not enough, is it?
That's not true.
It's a huge help having you here.
I'm glad you think so.
But we can't seem to recover any helpful memories.
That's true.
Watch out!
The light's red.
I'm sorry!
It's dangerous to space out like that.
This has happened before, too.
You don't remember me, do you?
Of course not.
Goodbye, then.
Have you met him before?
Just now, I felt something flutter in my chest.
Me too.
Wow!
What a beautiful view!
Plus, this is my first time riding in one of these!
Ah, we're here!
What a nice place.
Yeah.
Hey, Shin's looking over at you again.
I wonder why. It looks like there's something he really wants to say.
Do you think he knows that you lost your memory?
Wasn't it supposed to be clear this weekend with 0% chance of rain, Ken?
That was the forecast during the week,
but the weather changes rapidly.
What can you do?
What a downpour!
Now, everyone. I think this rain will end soon.
I don't see any sign of that. How do you figure?
I can tell by the smell.
I see.
Smell, huh?
Can you really predict the weather by smell?
It doesn't look like it's going to stop.
You told me to promise you just one thing.
Kento?
I wonder what the promise was.
Yeah.
It stopped raining.
Wow, Waka was right! The rain really stopped!
It stopped just like he said it would.
That's kind of amazing.
It is.
What kind of smell does rain have?
Was that...
What is it? Is there something on my face?
Oh, no. It's nothing.
You look like you've been daydreaming.
How can he tell?
Hey, let's ask him about the vision you saw.
Um, as I was listening to the rain, I remembered the festival we went to before.
There were lots of pretty wind chimes in the merchant stalls,
and while it drizzled, you let me under your umbrella.
He's so inexpressive again!
You remember, don't you?
We were at a festival?
Hey!
We're over here!
From the looks of it, Kento doesn't know what you're talking about.
But all the visions you've seen up until now have been too disjointed, and there isn't anything connecting them.
The people in them are always different, too.
I wonder what's going on.
I don't know.
I wonder if they're experiences I had before I lost my memories.
Now then!
While we wait for the meteor shower, let's play a game!
Team air hockey, go!
The first contenders are...
Shin and Toma
versus Kento and Ikki!
Shin, you're on offense, I'm on defense.
Is that all right?
Of course. There isn't any other formation.
Hm...
Looks like some people are blurting out their strategy.
I wonder if they're underestimating us.
Of course not. You're good at this kind of game, aren't you, Ikki?
You're in the table tennis club, right?
Wrong. I'm in the darts circle now.
I'm good at almost any game that uses my hands.
That's pretty much all games.
You don't need a strategy meeting?
It's already decided.
I'll come up with the plan, and Ikkyu will do the fighting.
Hey, Ken.
Ikkyu? He means Ikki, right?
You don't have to be polite and reveal our strategy, too.
Is that a nickname?
Now it's fair. We'll just show them that they'll still lose.
His real name?
Either way, it doesn't suit him at all!
I'm the one who has to do the work.
Not that I mind.
They sure talk big.
Well, we don't plan on losing either.
Okay, it looks like both teams are ready, so let the game begin!
All right!
Show them a false opening.
Kento and Ikki win!
Ikki is seriously just too good.
No, Kento's flawless strategies are really something, too.
Damn... I don't think I can win in a game that uses hands.
I know, cards.
Let's play poker.
Fine with me.
But like I said before, I'm good at any game that uses my hands.
Huh?
Well, poker uses hands in a different sense.
I'm seriously starting to think there's no winning against Ikki.
Sorry about that.
I'm glad we came after all.
That's true. Thank you, Orion.
But I haven't done anything.
I'm sure I couldn't've done this alone.
Just having you here is a huge help.
I see. I'm glad.
You know, I'm happy that I'm with you, too.
I know getting your memories back is the top priority,
but I'm happy I get to experience all these new things with you.
Orion.
Hey.
It's our turn next.
Oh, right.
Let's beat the crap out of Waka and Mine!
Okay?
Okay!
The Mnemid meteor shower.
It is said that those who see it will etch wonderful memories into their hearts.
I hope that tonight will be a wonderful memory.
Mr. Manager, how much further?
Just a little further.
You said that before.
This time I mean it.
This is pretty tough.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
You tried hard at air hockey, so maybe you've used up all your strength.
But good job beating the manager!
Yeah. I surprised myself.
The manager's puck disappeared for a second, too!
You did well to hit it back.
I had my eyes closed the whole time.
What? So you hit that by chance?
Well, it was fun either wa—
Huh?
Shin.
You're exhausted, aren't you?
Not... at all.
Here.
Give me your hand.
Come on, just give it.
I'm fine by myself.
You know,
there's something I want to ask you.
I think being alone with him is a bad idea right now!
We don't know what he's going to ask.
You have to make up an excuse!
Um... We should catch up to the others,
or they'll worry.
That was dangerous.
I'm okay.
I'm fine. So...
I killed...
I...
...killed a man.
Not that way!
Now I have no choice.
I guess I should take this to them.
No...
It's no use.
Because this is where he...
I'm coming in.
Hey.
How long are you going to sleep for?
Shin?
It's already ten.
Huh?
August 1st?
You're half asleep, aren't you?
Seriously.
What are you spacing out for?
Let me snap you out of it.
My vision wavers like a dream
The ones I see daily
have no true color or light
Hear the distant roll of thunder?
That's my love
This world is made of melted snow
I held out my hand
Where are we in this darkness?
I've woken up, and nothing happens
Wake me up
Warm rays of light strike my cheeks
The wind bids to me
outside the window
I don't understand
I force open the door
and a little voice crosses my consciousness
The girl in me sings to my mind
What is it?
Aren't you going to freak out in embarrassment today?
You are really out of it.
I'll sign the forms to get you discharged, so get dressed by then.
When I get back, I'll come in without saying anything.
Um...
Discharge? What is he talking about?
Orion, I think I...
Orion?
Hey,
what's going on,
Orion?
Do you know the trick to winning in air hockey?
To maintain a strong defense, no matter what.
You can't let your opponent score a single point.
The best offense is a strong defense.
Or is it the other way around?
Also, boys shouldn't ride in swan boats together.